Chengze, something happened
They got the original copy
Elder Qin is also here
Su Mingyao has a backup from six months ago
Old things can speak
Evidence can speak too
Mr Gu may sit in
But do not interfere with the verification
Miss Su
Please tell us exactly what happened that day
I'm really not trying to fight for anything
If that person is really Mr Fu
I can't hide it
It was raining heavily that day
I was at Qinghe Orphanage
And I saw a young boy nearby
He was leaning against the wall
With a crescent-shaped wound on his left wrist
I was really scared
But I still ran to get help
Later I went with him to
Nancheng Third Community Hospital
Which door did you enter through